Last night, I heard your name, you know it felt the same
They told me, you moved back into your place
You're so close yet so far, I always wonder how you are
From the morning's light to the night's embrace
We move in waves, hopeless fate
'Cause I know, it's who we are
We've tried it all
On and off, and I know
We're far from the best time we've ever known
So much time has passed now, and you never called
We used to be close, sharing each other's views
Will you let me in somehow?
Let me in without falling in love
Falling in love, falling in love
With someone else
Last time I saw your face, felt the depth of your gaze
Through your eyes, I felt I always belonged
But when you met someone, we got lost and didn't talk
This complicated dance, we didn't try to end
I lost myself in countless ways
But I know, it's who we are
We've tried it all
On and off, and I know
We're far from the best time we've ever known
So much time has passed, now you never called
We used to be close, sharing each other's views
Will you let me in somehow?
Let me in without falling in love
Falling in love, falling in love
With someone else, mmm